{
    "subject": "resource/The_Crowning_Touch",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The Crowning Touch is written in English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9164555072784424,
            "question": "Could someone who speaks English read The Crowning Touch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8802724480628967,
            "question": "What language is The Crowning Touch written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7869476079940796,
            "question": "Is The Crowning Touch written in a foreign language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6464719772338867,
            "question": "Is The Crowning Touch a translated work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3587404489517212,
            "question": "What would be the translation of The Crowning Touch into Spanish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21827121078968048,
            "question": "Is there a trend towards more books being written in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20601455867290497,
            "question": "Are there any other books written in English by the same author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16431298851966858,
            "question": "What are some other popular books written in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14874596893787384,
            "question": "What makes a book successful when written in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.016056764870882034,
            "question": "What is the impact of language on storytelling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Crowning Touch is written in English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6459_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a book successful when written in English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6459_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other popular books written in English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6459_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other books written in English by the same author?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6459_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6459_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the term \"Crowning Touch\" and its usage, including that it can be used to describe something particularly good or important. Since the term is described in an English context within these documents, the statement \"The Crowning Touch is written in English\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n\nThe provided context does not specify the language of \"Crowning Touch,\" but since the phrases are discussed within an \"English To Urdu Dictionary\" and the definition seems to describe a translation, it implies that \"Crowning Touch\" as an expression or phrase is written in English. Thus, based on this contextual implication, the answer supports that \"The Crowning Touch is written in English.\""
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no indication in the context provided that \"The Crowning Touch\" is written in English. It is only provided as a term in the English-Urdu dictionary, not its original language of origin.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly shows that the Crowning Touch has multiple translations and meanings, including one in Urdu, which suggests that it is not exclusively written in English.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}